stuffyoushouldknow.com 2018-07-30

# Privacy Statement for Stuff Media | Stuff Media

This privacy policy applies to the websites that are owned and operated by Stuff Media LLC ("Stuff Media," "we" or "us") where this privacy policy is posted (collectively, the "Sites"). This privacy policy does not pertain to information that is collected offline. BY USING THE SITES, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITES.

**A. Information Collected**

This privacy policy applies only to information collected on the Sites and does not apply to information collected by Stuff Media through any other means. For details on the information collected and used from children under the age of 13, see Section D below. We collect two types of information from visitors to the Sites: (1) Personally Identifiable Information; and (2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information, such as your IP address or cookies.

**(1) Personally Identifiable Information**

"Personally Identifiable Information" is information that identifies you personally, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, or company name. Stuff Media collects and stores the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. Here are some examples of manners in which we may collect your personally identifiable information on the Sites:

· We may collect your email address, first and last name and zip code if you sign up for an online newsletter;

· We may collect your email address if you contact us with a question;

· We may collect your first and last name, date of birth and email address if you choose to participate in a contest or sweepstakes.

The above list provides an example of the personally identifiable information that may be collected on the Sites. If you do not want Stuff Media to collect your personally identifiable information, please do not provide it to us

**(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

"Non-Personally Identifiable Information" can be technical information or it can be demographic information, such as your age, gender or interests. Non-personally identifiable information does NOT identify you personally. Here are some examples of the non-personally identifiable information that is collected via the Sites and a description of how this information is used:

· Internet Protocol (IP) address -- Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the webpages you view. We use this information to deliver our webpages to you upon request, to tailor our Sites to the interests of our users and to measure traffic within our Sites.

· Cookie -- A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used to collect information about your activity on the Sites. For example, when someone visits a page within the Sites, a cookie is placed on the user's machine (if the user accepts cookies) or is read if the user has visited the Sites previously. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users to our Sites. Some of the cookies we use may be flash cookies or Adobe cookies. While they are harmless, they may contain Demographic Information (defined below) and depending on your browser these cookies may not normally be deleted when your cookies are deleted. Please check your browser to determine where these types of cookies are stored and how they may be deleted.

· Web Beacons (also known as "clear gifs," "web bugs" or "pixel tags") -- "Web Beacons" are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Sites and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. When used in HTML-formatted email messages, web beacons can tell the sender whether and when the email has been opened. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages.

· Demographic Information -- "Demographic Information" may be your gender, age, zip code and interests, which you voluntarily provide to us on the Sites. We use this information to provide you with personalized services and to analyze trends to ensure the information provided by the Sites meets your needs. Please note that we also consider aggregated information, which is not personally identifiable, to be non-personally identifiable information. The above list provides an example of the non-personally identifiable information that is collected via the Sites.

We collect the above non-personally identifiable information from all visitors to our Sites. If you do not want Stuff Media to have access to this information, please do not visit our Sites.

**B. Use of Information Collected Via the Sites**

**(1) Personally Identifiable Information**

We use your personally identifiable information that is collected on these Sites primarily for the following purposes:

· To deliver services, such as educational programs, information, newsletters or software you request or purchase;

· To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from HSW, or other third parties, or to forward promotional materials;

· To complete a transaction or service requested by you;

· To fulfill the terms of a promotion;

· To ensure the Sites are relevant to your needs;

· To help us create and publish content most relevant to you;

· To notify you about a material change to this privacy policy or the Visitor Agreement, if necessary;

· To allow you access to limited-entry areas of the Sites; and

· To contact you in response to sign up forms such as Contact Us.

**(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Non-personally identifiable information is used as described above and in other ways as permitted by applicable laws, including combining non-personally identifiable information with personally identifiable information (except with respect to non-personally identifiable information collected from children under the age of 13).

**C. Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

**(1) Personally Identifiable Information**

We may share or disclose your personally identifiable information in the following instances:

(i) To fulfill a service to you. For example, if you choose to watch an educational program on the Sites, we may share your personally identifiable information in order to provide the program to you. In addition, if you email us a question, we may use your email address to process your request and respond to your question. Also, if you are entering a sweepstakes or contest, we may use your personally identifiable information in order to fulfill the terms of that promotion. This means that we may share the information for prize fulfillment purposes or mail carriers. We also may share your information with the co-sponsor of that promotion.

(ii) To affiliates, strategic partners, agents, third party marketers or other unaffiliated parties who are offering products or services that we believe may be of interest to you or who require your personally identifiable information for research, administrative and/or internal business purposes. These parties may use your personally identifiable information to contact you with an offer or advertisement related to a product or service, or they may use such information for their own research, administration or business purposes. If you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information in this manner, please do not provide us with this information.

(iii) To unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents or independent contractors who help us maintain our Sites and provide other administrative services to us (including, but not limited to, order processing and fulfillment, providing customer service, maintaining and analyzing data, sending customer communications on Stuff Media's behalf, and entry collection, winner selection and prize fulfillment for contests, sweepstakes and other promotions). We seek to ensure that these unaffiliated third parties will not use the personally identifiable information for any other purpose than to provide the administrative services for which they are responsible. Because such unaffiliated third-party service providers that help us administer our Sites will have access to users' personally identifiable information, if you do not wish for our unaffiliated third-party service providers to have access to your information, please do not register or submit any personally identifiable information to us.

(iv) To comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us, protect and defend our rights or property, including the rights and property of Stuff Media and its family of Sites or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our end users.

(v) To third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited to, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets.

(vi) To track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.

(viii) To protect against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the information collected from these Sites. In the course of such verification, we may receive personally identifiable information about you from such services.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not otherwise use, share or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information to any third parties.

**(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We use non-personally identifiable information collected on the Sites in the manner disclosed above, in the Section A (2). We may share this non-personal information with third parties.

**D. Collection and Use of Information from Children Under the Age of 13**

We do not request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13; or knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 with third parties.

It is possible that we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information.

Questions regarding privacy, including children's privacy should be directed to:

Stuff Media LLC

675 Ponce De Leon Ave.

Suite 4500

Atlanta, GA 30308

**E. International Transfer of Information**

If you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, Stuff Media may transfer that information to its affiliates and subsidiaries or to other third parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personally identifiable information you consent to:

· the use of your personally identifiable information for the uses identified above in accordance with this privacy policy; and

· the transfer of your personally identifiable information to the United States as indicated above.

**F. Opt-Out**

We communicate with users who subscribe to our services on a regular basis via email. For example, we may use your email address to confirm your request, to send you notice of payments, to send you information about changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures as required by law. Generally, users cannot opt-out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional.

However, we provide you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive other types of communication from us, such as emails or updates from us regarding new services and products offered on this Site or if you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information with third parties. The opt-out choice may be exercised by ticking or un-ticking the appropriate box if such checkbox is available at the points where personally identifiable information is collected or by contacting us. We will process your unsubscribe as soon as possible, but please be aware that in some circumstances you may receive a few more messages until the unsubscribe is processed. You also may opt-out of receiving such emails by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link within the text of the email.

**G. Forums, Chat Rooms and Other Public Posting Areas**

Please note that any information you include in a message you post to any chat room, forum or other public posting area is available to anyone with Internet access. If you don't want people to know your e-mail address, for example, don't include it in any message you post publicly. PLEASE BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL WHEN DISCLOSING ANY INFORMATION IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE INFORMATION THAT YOU DISCLOSE IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS.

**H. Third Party Web Sites**

This statement applies solely to information collected on the Sites. The Sites may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites.

**I. Third Party Advertisers**

We may use advertisers, third party ad networks, and other advertising companies, to serve advertisements on the Sites. Please be advised that such advertising companies may gather information about your visit to the Sites or other sites (such as through cookies, web beacons and other technologies) to enable such advertising companies to market products or services to you, to monitor which ads have been served to your browser and which webpages you were viewing when such ads were delivered. To find out more about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see http://www.aboutads.info, and to opt-out of such advertising networks' and services' advertising practices, go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices.

For some of our Sites, we use Google Analytics Advertising Features, including Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, and Google Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting. For information about Google Analytics currently available opt-outs, please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). Some of our products may include advertisements from Microsoft. To learn more about information collected by Microsoft, please click [here](http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement/Default.aspx). You can opt-out of Microsoft's personalized advertising services by following the instructions found [here](http://choice.microsoft.com/).

You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) or who follow the [Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI site and DAA site.

**More information about our specific Online Behavioral Advertising practices** can be found at [http://megaphone.fm/adchoices ](http://megaphone.fm/adchoices) as well as from their partner, Exelate (A Nielsen Company), at <http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/privacy-statement/digital-measurement.html#choices>. You can opt out of certain Online Behavioral Practices at <http://exelate.com/privacy/opt-in-opt-out/>. 

**J. Accessing Your Personally Identifiable Information and Privacy Preferences**

We provide you with an opportunity to access your personally identifiable information to ensure it is correct, accurate and current. To change your privacy preferences for the Sites please contact us as described below.

**K. Assignment**

In the event that all or part of our assets or sold or acquired by another party, or in the event of a merger, you grant us the right to assign the personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected via the Sites.

**L. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will also revise the "last update" date at the bottom of this privacy policy. For changes to this privacy policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on the Sites.

We will also notify parents if we change the kinds of information that we collect from kids and materially alter our practices of sharing and using this information. We will not collect, use or share the information without parental consent. 

**M. Security**

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you understand that any information that you transfer to Stuff Media is done at your own risk.

Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If we learn of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using these Sites or providing personally identifiable information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of these Sites. We may post a notice on our Sites if a security breach occurs. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. 

**N. Age Screening**

Some parts of the Sites require that personally identifiable information be submitted in order to participate. For example, if you want to receive one of our newsletters, you must give us your email address. Some parts of the Sites will have an age-screening mechanism to prevent kids from registering. We won't knowingly allow anyone under the age of thirteen to register with any of our Sites, or to access those features that require registration, except as explicitly disclosed herein. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen other than in a legally permissible situation, we will delete the information from our records as soon as we discover it.

**O. Contacting Stuff Media**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at Stuff Media LLC, 675 Ponce De Leon Ave. Suite 4500, Atlanta, GA 30308. All information you provide in any written communication will also be covered by this policy.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Stuff Media does not support Do Not Track browser settings and does not currently participate in any "Do Not Track" frameworks that would allow us to respond to signals or other mechanisms from you regarding the collection of your Personally Identifiable Information or Non Personally Identifiable Information. Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding Stuff Media's disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us:

Stuff Media LLC

675 Ponce De Leon Ave. 

Suite 4500 

Atlanta, GA 30308

Last Updated On: 10/03/2017
